[{"answer": "Okay.", "docId": "321pets.htm.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "So what did you do today my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Yeah, come here", "docId": "321pets.htm.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Yeah. Oh! Was how you invented the cotton gin?", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "So? I mean have you thought about it", "docId": "321pets.htm.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Oh no, not the thing. I hate the thing. What's the thing", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I guess you can", "docId": "321pets.htm.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "All right", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Yeah, no, I'm fairly intuitive and psychic. It's a substantial gift", "docId": "321pets.htm.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Absolutely, oh I promise. Tell her what", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I stayed home from work today while you were at rehearsal so somebody could be here with our chick", "docId": "321pets.htm.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You don't think I get up when you get up", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "That's not what I said. Okay, I just meant..", "docId": "321pets.htm.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I don't know, maybe we weren't ready to have a chick", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Look, I'm fine. Watch.  Look at that.  Who", "docId": "321pets.htm.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "No. I have got to get ready and go to a dinner at my bosses house. It's a very big deal, there's a lot of people there I have to meet", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "my friend..", "docId": "321pets.htm.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Fine. I'll go", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Look, either help me or go", "docId": "321pets.htm.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " Okay, but before you go, could you help me first", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " Of course I am. I just have to make a call", "docId": "321pets.htm.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Okay?", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Does it involve clogs", "docId": "321pets.htm.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Clogs", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Hey", "docId": "321pets.htm.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I did! But the store wouldn't take her back! So then I took her to the shelter, and you know what I found out?", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I don't believe this! Wow, look at this refridgerator! It's gigantic! I mean I could live in this thing! I'd be cold, but I'm always cold. Oh my God, look at these spider burners! I love spider burners", "docId": "321pets.htm.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Oh, it is sooo perfect. Thank you so much.", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "No, it's not bad. It's not bad at all. It'", "docId": "321pets.htm.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "You may be okay about getting hurt, but I am not okay with being the one who hurts you. That's why I can't take this job", "qsentId": 30}]